A Guide to the James Whitcomb Riley Collection
University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library, #7133-u
James Whitcomb Riley Collection 1876-1928, n.d.
University of Virginia. Library. Special Collections Dept. Alderman Library University of Virginia Charlottesville, Virginia 22903 USA
7133-u
ca. 320 items
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Purchase
Item Listing
- Typescripts
  - Correspondence of Clara Bottsford and James Whitcomb Riley(ca. 25 items), 1876-1879
  - Correspondence of Clara Bottsford and James Whitcomb Riley(ca. 75 items), 1880
  - Correspondence of Clara Bottsford and James Whitcomb Riley(ca. 50 items), 1881
  - Correspondence of Clara Bottsford and James Whitcomb Riley(ca. 50 items), 1882
  - Correspondence of Clara Bottsford and James Whitcomb Riley(ca. 50 items), 1883
  - Correspondence of Clara Bottsford and James Whitcomb Riley(ca. 20 items), 1884
  - Correspondence of Clara Bottsford and James Whitcomb Riley(ca. 6 items)
  - Duplicate transcripts of Bottsford-Riley correspondence; introductory critical assessment of C. Bottsford with duplicates (ca. 30 items)
- Miscellaneous
  - Miscellaneous papers re: Riley estate, library count, etc. (ca. 5 items), 1928 Jan 9 & n.d.
- Photographs
  - 4 identical photographs of woman seated holding infant, Photos
  - 2 identical photographs of 2 gentlemen, 1 seated and 1 standing, Photos